

### MY CONTACT

Ingkhanh94@gmail.com

(+84) 93 882 6364

11/02/1994

125 Thoi Hoa, Vinh Loc A, Binh Chanh, Ho Chi Minh City

https://lngkhanh94.github.io

# SKILLS SUMMARY

- Strong communication skills
- Good experience in teamwork skills
- Analytical and problem-solving skills
- Management and planning skills
- Partner communication skills
- Presentation skills
- Reflection skills

#### RFFFRFNCF

Tien, Nguyen Manh (Mr.)

Email: tiennm15494@sacombank.com

Phone: (+84) 986 733 782

# KHANH, LE NGOC

# TECHNICAL LEAD

# **ABOUT ME**

I have seven years of software development and management experience, including three years in the roles of technical lead and project manager. My goal is to become a project management expert in the near future and become a future project manager

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### March 2019 - Present

Technical Lead of Application Development Center worker in Sai Gon Thuong Tin Commercial Joint Stock Bank

#### Key responsibilities:

- Manage the tasks and work progress of the team as a team leader.
- Reviewing design, technical, and operational solution documents related to the bank's online payment transactions.
- Participating in the development of projects to build new banking systems on the basis of micro-services and optimizing existing systems
- Provide a technical approach to software development that addresses business features; write overview architectural documents and coding conventions; manage teams; and guide developers to develop detailed blueprints for each function.
- Using technology to manage teams and projects Microsoft Project, Jira

#### August 2016 to March 2019

Senior System Development and Integration of Application Development Center worker in Saigon Thuong Tin Commercial Joint Stock Bank

#### Key responsibilities:

- Design and develop internal service applications that handle reporting requests from the business and integrate third-party applications and external services.
- Implement software development requirements and design an online transaction application system for Ecom, QR, POS, Ewallet, ATM, Card Service Bus, Integrated Core Card, and T24 Bank.
- Design and develop on-demand and integrated services with fintech organizations (Zalo, MoMo, etc.), domestic card organizations (Napas), and international Cybersource/Visa/Master.

# **Technology**

#### Languages:

- C# ASP.NET (.Net/Core)
- C/C++
- Java
- NodeJs
- ReactJS
- PHP

#### Database

- Microsoft SQL Server,
- IBM DB2
- Oracle

#### Server:

- · Windows Server
- Unix

#### Cache:

- Memory
- · Redis

#### Proxy:

- · Apache
- Nginx

#### Protocol

- HTTP/HTTPs
- TCP
- Socket
- SMTP
- FTP/FTPs/SFTP

#### Source control:

- Git lab
- Tortoise-SVN

#### Plan:

- Microsoft Project
- Iira/Confluence

#### Model:

- · Agile
- Waterfall

- Design system models to ensure continuous, stable, stateless, and scalable operation, with a mechanism to reduce the load on the system and database.
- Design responsive systems to switch between async and sync processing streams, have error handling mechanisms, and timeout when backend systems fail.
- The intensive programming language C# handles and solves mechanisms for multitasking, multithreading, memory leaks, high CPUs, and threads.
- Implement and participate in the development of integration axes: message queue, web or application server, caching, workflow orchestration, load balancer.

January 2016 to March 2016

Junior System Development at Thai Son Technology Development Company

#### Key responsibilities:

 Implemented in-house application software development using technology based on .Net platform using WinForms and Windows services

## **EDUCATION BACKGROUND**

Industrial University of Ho Chi Minh City

- Specialization in Information Technology
- I have participated in courses organized by FSOFT FPT [2015].
- I have participated in classes on web design faculty and courses organized by IBM [2014].

Completed in 2016

# **Achievements**

2022 - Project Management Certification FMIT PMI

2019 - Certificate of Completion of AWS Courses

2016 - ICTCC conference paper on MCPGA